

Skills:

- Phone repair and investigation;
- Blancco, 3UTools, Hemuli
- Scrum Framework
- Trello, Jira
- Google Sheets
- HTML/CSS, Figma
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- GitHub, VS Code

Languages:

Russian (Native) English (High Proficiency) Swedish (Intermediate)

Hobbies

Photography, coding, design & visual arts; hiking, cycling & running;

Maria Pokryshkina

mariapokryshkina@gmail.com

+358453262363

Profile

A Senior Repair Specialist with background in Information & Knowledge Management. Quality-oriented, goal-driven lifelong learner experienced in customer service and coding. Agile project work & analytical thinking, aiming to create a more efficient and productive workspace.

Experience

SENIOR REPAIR SPECIALIST

Helsinki Swappie Oy | March 2021 Phone Investigation & Repair; Welding; Blancco, 3UTools & Hemuli; Panic Logs Analysis; Internal Guidance and Workshops; Stocktaking;

FRONT-END DEVELOPER TRAINEE

Helsinki Tira Oy | August 2022 -November 2022 Programming (JavaScript, TypeScript);
Maintaining Code & Fixing Errors; Testing
& Implementing Software Functions;
Software Component Library
Implementation; UX & UI Design (Mockups
and Wireframes); Teamwork & Daily Scrum;

SALESPERSON

Helsinki Trumpbell Oy February 2018 - March 2020 Direct sales; Customer Consulting &
Communication; Returns & Complaints;
Stocking Merchandise and Creating
Displays; Sales Optimization & Promotions;

SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH DEPARTMENT SPECIALIST

Petrozavodsk PetrSu|September 2015 -July 2016 Cross-department Communication & Formal Correspondence; Documentation Records; Translation of Documents and Academic Articles; Working with Academic Databases; Negotiations; Resource Planning & organisational matters;

Education

HELSINKI BUSINESS COLLEGE

Full-Stack Web Developer

Helsinki August 2021 - December 2022 HTML5 and CSS3; UI / UX Design and Prototyping(Figma); Programming JavaScript; Typescript; Data structures; React & Redux; Node & Express; Unit Testing & Quality Assurance; Continuous Integrations and AWS; Working in a Software Development Team; Software Development Project (in collaboration with PHZ Full Stack);

ÅBO AKADEMI UNIVERSITY

Master of Economics and Business Administration - MBA

Turku August 2016 - May 2020 Information & Knowledge Management; Information Architecture; Competitive Intelligence; Information Management; Information Strategies; Sustainable Business; Intercultural Marketing Management; Management on Industrial Brands; Business Analytics; Project Management; Financial Economics;

Projects

Software Development Project in collaboration with PHZ Full-Stack

Helsinki March2022 - May 2022

In this project our team collaborates with PHZ Full-Stack in order to create a NPS (Net Promoter Score) application. Such application enables users to use the dashboard for creating their own surveys which could be further integrated into any web-platform. An app is created using React.js, Material UI. Tasks are communicated through Trello, while code is shared and maintained via GitHub.

Links

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/maria-pokryshkina0251214b/

GitHub: https://github.com/mariapokryshkina